Guide to the Doris Duke papers on the Shangri La residence, 1932-2003 and undated RL.01434
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Architectural Records, 1932-1940 and undated, approximately 180 items
  - Section "D-D" Looking North, Section "E-E" Looking East, Section "F-F" Looking East, Section "G-G" Looking North, Dr'wg 8. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Mar 11. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F1)
  - Plan of Tennis Court, Alleé & Garage, Dr'wg 12. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Jul 19. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F1)
  - Floor Plan Upper Level, Dr'wg 101. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Jun 7. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F2)
  - Detail Plan of Bedrm. Wing. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Apr 10. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F2)
  - Detail Plan of So. Serv. Wing, Dr'wg 104. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Apr 23. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F2)
  - Plan of East and North Service Wings, Dr'wg 105. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Apr 21. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F2)
  - Plan of Dining Rm. Section, Dr'wg 106. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 May 25. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F2)
  - Detail of Living Rm. Chimney, Dr'wg 107-A. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 May 7. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F2)
  - Construction Details Stair to Basement, Dr'wg 109. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Apr 22. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F2)
  - Sect. Thru Serv. Area Looking Makai (S) on [illegible] of Living Room; Makai (S) Elev. Of Service Wing, Dr'wg 111. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Apr 30. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F2)
  - Elev. Of Service Area Stairway Looking North; Sec. Thru Service Court Looking Mauka (N); Mauka (N) Elevation of Service Wing Looking South; Sec. Thru Service Court Looking Koko HD (East), Dr'wg 112. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Apr 30. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F2)
  - Dining Rm Wing: Lower Level, Dr'wg 113. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Apr 30. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F2)
  - Section Thru Entrance Foyer, Plan & Section Thru Glass Block, Dr'wg 115. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 May 10. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F2)
  - Entrance Elevation Looking (S); West Elevation B.R. Wing; South Elev. B.R. Wing, Dr'wg 116. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 June 1. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F2)
  - Sec. Mr. Cromwell B.R., Sec. Mrs. Cromwell's Bedroom, Dr'wg 118. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 June 18. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F2)
  - Section Mr. & Mrs. Cromwell's Bd. Rm. Wing, Dr'wg 119. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 June 4. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F2)
  - Details of Openings Mrs. Cromwell's Bedroom, Dr'wg 120A. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Aug 27. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F2)
  - Roof Plan Bedroom Wing, Dr'wg 122. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Jun 10. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F3)
  - Construction Sections of Patio, Living Room & Living Rm Hall, Dr'wg 123. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Jun 15. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F3)
  - Isometric Section Thru Roof Terrace Steps, Dr'wg 125. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Jun 19. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F3)
  - Part Roof Plan Guest Dr. Rm., Bath, & Entrance Foyer, Patio; Part Section Thru Guest Dr. Rm. & Entrance Foyer Looking (N); Section Thru Patio Looking (N) Towards Entrance Foyer, Dr'wg 127. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect (drawn by "J.P."). 1937 May 12. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F3)
  - Final Scheme for Clg. in Mrs. C's Dressing Rm, Dr'wg 130. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. Circa 1938. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F3)
  - Mrs. Cromwell's Bedroom, Dr'wg 131. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Jun 30. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F3)
  - Elevation of Guest Room, Sect. Guest Room Roof, Dr'wg 132. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Jul 2. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F3)
  - Interior Elev. Guest Dressing Room & Entry, Dr'wg 133. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Jul 3. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F3)
  - Sections Thru East Hall, Dr'wg 134. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Jul 6. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F3)
  - Plan of Entrance Court & Steps to Allee, Dr'wg 137. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Jun 19. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F3)
  - Mrs. Cromwell's Bedroom Wing, Elev. & Sect. of Entrance Court and Pools, Dr'wg 138. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Jul 28. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F3)
  - Plan & Interior Elevations of Mr. Cromwell's Bedroom, Dr'wg 141. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Aug 30. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F3)
  - Plan of Living Room, Dr'wg 143. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Sep 14. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F3)
  - Detail of Living Room Steps at Four Makai Openings, Dr'wg 145. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Apr 26. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F3)
  - Bronze Sash Schedule, Dr'wg 146. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Sep 14. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F3)
  - Half Plan Sliding Bay Window Guest Room, Dr'wg 147. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Sep 14. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Typ. Det. Living Room Sliding Sash Opening, Dr'wg 149. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Sep 14. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Det. Thru Bay Window, Guest Room, Dr'wg 150. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Sep 14. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - 3" Scale Detail of Window M/20, Mr. Cromwell's Bedrm, Dr'wg 152. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Sep 17. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - 3" Scale Details of Clerestory of Entrance Foyer, Dr'wg 153. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Sep 20. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Details of Exterior Opngs., Mr. C's Bedrm, Dr'wg 154. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Sep 28. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Revised Plan, Entrance Foyer & Main Stair, Dr'wg 155. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Oct 8. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Ceiling & Roof Plan, Entrance Foyer & Stairs, Dr'wg 156. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Oct 8. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Entrance Foyer, Main Stair and Patio, Dr'wg 157. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Sep 28. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Revised Details of Doors U/21 and U/22 in Entresol, Dr'wg 157-A. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1938 Jun 6. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Entrance Foyer, Section "C-C" (Looking North), Dr'wg 158. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Oct 8. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Entrance Foyer & Main Stairway, Section "D-D" (Looking South), Dr'wg 159. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Oct 8. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Main Stair & Screen Elevation from Patio, Dr'wg 160. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Oct 8. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Sections E-E and F-F, Main Stairway, Dr'wg 163. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Oct 8. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Sections E-E and F-F, Main Stairway, Dr'wg 163-A. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect (drawn by "J.P."). 1937 Dec 29. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Ceiling Plan of Living Room, Dr'wg 164. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Oct 8. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Interior Elev. Living Room, Dr'wg 165. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Oct 8. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Paving of Coral-Sandstone in Patio & on Main Stairs, Dr'wg 232. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1938 Jun 4. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F4)
  - Interior Elev. of Living Room (Looking South), Dr'wg 166. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Oct 8. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Full Size Details of Medicine Cabinet, Full Size Details of Mirror Window Shelves, Dr'wg 169. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Dec 3. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Revised Floor & Ceiling Plan of Patio, Dr'wg 170. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Oct 30. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Kitchen & Pantry Casework, Dr'wg 171. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Oct 28. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Mrs. Cromwell's Bedroom, Detail Showing Rad. of Ceiling and Cove Light, Dr'wg 173. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Oct 21. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Roofing Details Section Thru Vent Opngs Mauka Side of D. Rm. Wing, Dr'wg 174. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Nov 5. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Part Plan & Section Showing Interior Elev. L.R. West End, Dr'wg 176. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Nov 17. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Floor Pattern in Living Rm & L.R. Hall, Dr'wg 179. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Nov 29. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Plan of Vent Ducts for Toilet Rooms, Dr'wg 180. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Apr 27. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Grilles & Louvres, Types 1 to 7, Dr'wg 186. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Dec 13 Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Grilles & Louvres - 8, 9, 10, Dr'wg 187. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Dec 14. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Plan, Reflected Ceiling Plan & Elevations Living Rm Hall & Ent. Vest, Dr'wg 188. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Sep 28. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Detail Guest Room, Dr'wg 192. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Dec 24. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - 1½" Scale Details of Sash Weight Conditions in Basement Under Dining Room, Dr'wg 193. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Dec 28. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Vent Ducts Mr. Cromwell's Wardrobe & Linen Room, Dr'wg 194. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Jan 5. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Plan & Elevation of Guest Bathroom, Dr'wg 195. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Jan 7. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Detail of Pattern L.R. Fireplace, Dr'wg 218. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Apr 5. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - North Elevation of Living Room Showing Arched Fireplace with Wood Facing, Dr'wg 226-A. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1938 Jun 6. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Full Size Detail for Grilles Over Openings, Mrs. Cromwell's Bedroom (9 required), Dr'wg 571. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Nov 10. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Full Size Detail for Grilles Over Mrs. Cromwell's Bathroom, Dr'wg 573. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Nov 16. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Pair of Sliding Shutters Entry to Powder Rm, Dr'wg 288. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Nov 12. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F5)
  - Detail Linen Room Closet #10, Dr'wg 223-A. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Oct 18. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F6)
  - Detail Pair of Doors from Dining Room Porch to Moon Garden, Dr'wg 250. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Sep 15. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F6)
  - Black Lava Stone Flooring Pattern Dining Room, Dr'wg 253. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Sep 15. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D10F6)
  - Detail of Persian Doors to Men's Room, Dr'wg 265. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Sep 30. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F6)
  - Plans, Elevs. & Sects. Of Birdhouse, Dr'wg 266. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1938 Oct 4. Diazo; diazo, pencil and crayon. (Oversize-folder C1D10F6)
  - Detail of Canal Lights & Fountain, Dr'wg 268. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. Circa 1938. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F6)
  - Sketch Entry Vestibule Top Basement Stairs. [Marion Sims Wyeth, architect]. 1938 Sep 29. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F6)
  - Section Thru Waterfall at Steps to Alleé, Dr'wg 269. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. Circa 1938. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F6)
  - Detail Shell Cabinet Dining Room, Dr'wg 270. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Oct 12. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F6)
  - Detail of Display Case Living Room Hall, Dr'wg 271. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Oct 18. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F6)
  - Detail of Mrs. Cromwell's Wardrobe, Dr'wg 272. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Oct 18. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F6)
  - Diagram of Dining Rm. Columns, Dr'wg 273. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Oct 20. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D10F6)
  - Detail of Door From Basement to Boat Harbor, Dr'wg 517. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Apr 26. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F7)
  - Detail of Display Cabinet in Living Rm, Dr'wg 554. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Oct 3. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F7)
  - F.S. Details of Dining Rm. Cols. Conditions at Columns II, III, IV, V, Dr'wg 561. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Oct 20. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D10F7)
  - F.S. Details of Dining Rm. Columns Conditions at Column I, Dr'wg 562. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Oct 20. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D10F7)
  - Plans & Details, Garage for Mr. & Mrs. JHR Cromwell, Dr'wg G-1. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Oct 28. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F7)
  - Detail of Screen Openings at Lanai, Garage for Mr. & Mrs. JHR Cromwell, Dr'wg G-2. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Oct 28. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F7)
  - Interior Sections & Details of Garage, Dr'wg G-3. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. undated. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F7)
  - Garage Details, Dr'wg G-4. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Nov 20. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F7)
  - Detail of Sliding Sash Frame & Pocket, Garage Building, Dr'wg G-5. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Dec 5. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F7)
  - Revised Details of Louvres at Living Rm., Garage Building, Dr'wg G-6. Marion Sims Wyeth and H. Drewry Baker, architects. 1937 Dec 11. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F7)
  - Proposed Changes to Garage Bldg. for Mr. & Mrs. J.H.R. Cromwell, Dr'wg G-7. Wyeth & King, architects. 1939 Apr 11. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F7)
  - Detail of Door Back of Playhouse to Shore, Dr'wg PH-51. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. Circa 1938. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F7)
  - Schedule of New Doors for Playhouse, Dr'wg PH-52. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Sep 22. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F7)
  - Record Drawing Plan at Basement Level West End, Dr'wg R-1. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect (drawn by "J.P."). 1939 Apr 10. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F8)
  - Record Drawing Plan at Basement Level East End, Dr'wg R-2. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect (drawn by "J.P."). 1939 Apr 10. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F8)
  - Record Drawing Plan at Main Floor Level East End and West End, Dr'wg R-3, R-4. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect (drawn by "J.P."). 1939 Apr 10. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F8)
  - Record Drawing Plan at Upper Level West End, Dr'wg R-5. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect (drawn by "J.P."). 1939 Apr 10. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F8)
  - Record Drawing Plan at Roof Level, Dr'wg R-6. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect (drawn by "J.P."). 1939 Apr 10. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F8)
  - Record Drawing Sections & Elevations, Dr'wg R-7. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect (drawn by "J.P."). 1939 Apr 10. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F8)
  - Record Drawing Sections & Elevations, Dr'wg R-8. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect (drawn by "J.P."). 1939 Apr 10. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F8)
  - Record Drawing Elevations & Sections, Dr'wg R-9. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect (drawn by "J.P."). 1939 Apr 10. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F8)
  - Record Drawing Elevation & Sections, Dr'wg R-10. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect (drawn by "J.P."). 1939 Apr 10. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F8)
  - First Division, Zone 3, Sec. 1, Plat 41, Containing Parcels. 1932 Aug. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C1D10F9)
  - [Tax Map of Shangri La and adjoining property owners]. [Tax Maps]. [1932 Aug]. Photocopy (Oversize-folder C1D10F9)
  - Honolulu, Territory of Hawaii. Wright, Harvey & Wright, surveyors and civil engineers. 1934. Ferrogallic print. (Oversize-folder C1D10F9)
  - Topographic Map of Doris Duke Cromwell Property, Kaalawai, Honolulu, Oahu, T.H. Wright, Harvey & Wright, surveyors and civil engineers. 1936 Apr 16. Diazo; pen and crayon. (Oversize-folder C1D10F9)
  - Sketch for Proposed Mirror over Mrs. Cromwell's Fireplace. [Marion Sims Wyeth, architect]. 1938 Sep 13. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F9)
  - South Interior Elevation L.R., A, C, & D. [Wyeth & King, architects]. 1938 May 13. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F9)
  - Section Thru Dining Rm Looking Mauka Showing Shell Cabinet, F. Wyeth & King, architects. 1938 Sep 21. Pencil and colored pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F9)
  - Detail of Door Opening From Living Room Hall to Dining Room Entry, G. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect]. 1938 Sep 22. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F9)
  - Plan at Recess in Entrance Vestibule And Display Cabinet L.R. Hall, H. [Wyeth & King, architects]. 1938 Sep 22. Diazo; diazo, pencil and colored pencil. (Oversize-folder C1D10F9)
  - Sketch Elevation Guest Room (Looking North), K. [Wyeth & King, architects]. 1938 Sep 29. Diazo and colored pencil. (Oversize-folder C1D10F9)
  - Mauka Wall of Living Rm. Showing Cabinets, N. [Wyeth & King, architects]. Circa 1938. Diazo; diazo and pencil. (Oversize-folder C1D10F9)
  - Elevation of Fountain at Head of Canal, T. [Wyeth & King, architects]. Circa 1938. Diazo; pencil and crayon. (Oversize-folder C1D10F9)
  - [Staircase], U. [Wyeth & King, architects] and H. Drewry Baker, architect. 1938 Oct 13. Diazo; diazo, pencil and crayon. (Oversize-folder C1D10F9)
  - Untitled, circa 1938. Pencil and colored pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F9)
  - Mr. Drew Baker's Sketches of Honolulu House. H Drewry Baker, architect. Circa 1938. Negative photostat print. (Oversize-folder C1D10F10)
  - [Blue Tile Facing Plans]. 1939 Dec 17. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D10F10)
  - Plan & Section of Kwan-Yin Room Showing Condition at Ceiling & Size of Cabinet. H Drewry Baker, architect. 1940 Dec 17. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D10F10)
  - Adjestment [sic] of Measured Mughal Fireplace in Existing Room. J. Chisty, architect and engineer. 196[4] Apr 3. Positive photostat print. (Oversize-folder C1D10F11)
  - Additions & Alterations To "Shangri-La," for Miss Doris Duke, Diamond Head, Hon., T.H. - Floor Plan, Drawing 1. Albert Ely Ives, architect. 1958 Oct 2. Diazo with colored pencil. (Oversize-folder C1D10F11)
  - Additions & Alterations To "Shangri-La," for Miss Doris Duke, Diamond Head, Hon., T.H. - Makai, Koko Head, and Diamond Head Elevations, Drawing 2. Albert Ely Ives, architect. 1958 Oct 2. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F11)
  - Additions & Alterations To "Shangri-La," for Miss Doris Duke, Diamond Head, Hon., T.H. - Makai Elevation, Drawing 3. Albert Ely Ives, architect. 1958 Oct 2. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D10F11)
  - [Master Bedroom Mughal Fireplace]. [John Sanderson, Jr., architect]. Undated. Photograph. (Oversize-folder C1D10F11)
  - [Master Bedroom Mughal Fireplace]. John Sanderson, Jr., architect. Undated. Photograph. (Oversize-folder C1D10F11)
  - [Master Bedroom Mughal Fireplace]. John Sanderson, Jr., architect. Undated. Photograph. (Oversize-folder C1D10F11)
  - [11 sheets of sketches on drafting paper]. [Wyeth & King]. Undated. Pencil and colored pencil drawings. (Oversize-folder C1D10F11)
  - [Aviary]. Christy Bros. 1960 Jul 3. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D10F11)
  - Proposed Lake Front Residence for Mr. & Mrs. JHR Cromwell Palm Beach Fla., Plan of First Floor. Treanor & Fatio, architects. 1935 Jun 14. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder SL1)
  - Estate of Mr. and Mrs. JHR Cromwell, Palm Beach, Florida. Treanor & Fatio. 1935 Aug 8. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder SL1)
  - Estate of Mr. and Mrs. JHR Cromwell, Palm Beach, Florida, First Floor Plan, Scheme "C". Treanor & Fatio. 1935 Aug 8. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder SL1)
  - Estate of Mr. and Mrs. JHR Cromwell, Palm Beach, Florida, First Floor Plan, Scheme "D". Treanor & Fatio. 1935 Aug 8. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder SL1)
  - Estate of Mr. and Mrs. JHR Cromwell, Palm Beach, Florida, Second Floor Plan, Scheme "D". Treanor & Fatio. 1935 Aug 8. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder SL1)
  - Additions and Alterations to "Shangri-La" for Miss Doris Duke, Floor Plan, Sheet 1. Albert Ely Ives, architect. 1958 Oct 2. Diazo with colored pencil. (Oversize-folder SL1)
  - Additions and Alterations to "Shangri-La" for Miss Doris Duke, Makai Elevation, Koko Head Elevation, Mauka Elevation, Diamond Head Elevation, Sheet 2. Albert Ely Ives, architect. 1958 Oct 2. Diazo with colored pencil. (Oversize-folder SL1)
  - Floor Pattern for Private Hall-Lanai-L.R. Portico, House for Mr. & Mrs. JHR Cromwell. 1938 Feb 18. Positive Photostat. (Oversize-folder SL1)
  - [Electrical System for Shangri La]. Undated. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder SL1)
  - Map Showing Lot 2 Judd Hillside Lots, Dr. R.J. Mansfield-Owner. Cain & Awana, engineering and landscaping. 1937 May. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder SL2)
  - Photo Contour Map of Portions of Honolulu. R.N. Towill, civil engineer & surveyor. 1952 Nov. Diazo. (Oversize-folder SL2)
  - F.S. Detail of Dining Room Cols. Conditions at Cols. II, III, IV, Dwg 560. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Oct 20. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder TU206)
  - Detail of Tile Facing on Stairway, Dwg 261. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Sep 27. Diazo. (Oversize-folder TU206)
  - Detail of Arch at L.R.H. Niches, Dwg 557. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1938 Oct 18. Diazo. (Oversize-folder TU206)